class QuizBrain {
  QuizBrain(
      {required this.question,
      required this.c1,
      required this.c2,
      required this.c3,
      required this.c4,
      required this.answer});

  String question;
  String c1;
  String c2;
  String c3;
  String c4;
  String answer;
}

List<QuizBrain> phyData = [
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'What is the value of gravitational constant?',
      c1: '6.6743 × 10^(-11)',
      c2: '6.9783 × 10^(-11)',
      c3: '9.9748 × 10^(-11)',
      c4: '6.6743 × 10^(-9)',
      answer: '6.6743 × 10^(-11)'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'The unit of electric dipole moment is',
      c1: 'newton',
      c2: 'coulomb',
      c3: 'farad',
      c4: 'debye',
      answer: 'debye'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'S.I. unit of flux is',
      c1: 'ohm',
      c2: 'weber',
      c3: 'tesla',
      c4: 'none',
      answer: 'weber'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'What is the index of refraction for perfect vacuum?',
      c1: '0',
      c2: '1',
      c3: '1.5',
      c4: '0.5',
      answer: '1'),
  QuizBrain(
      question:
          'Who among the following is credited for the discovery of Expanding Universe?',
      c1: 'Edwin Hubble',
      c2: 'Niels Bohr',
      c3: 'S Chandra Shekhar',
      c4: 'C V Raman',
      answer: 'Edwin Hubble'),
];
List<QuizBrain> chemData = [
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'The largest component of Coal gas is?',
      c1: 'Methane',
      c2: 'Hydrogen',
      c3: 'Carbon Dioxide',
      c4: 'Carbon Monoxide',
      answer: 'Hydrogen'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'Which of the following is the softest metal?',
      c1: 'Cesium',
      c2: 'Lead',
      c3: 'Gold',
      c4: 'Silver',
      answer: 'Cesium'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'How many electrons can the s-orbital accommodate?',
      c1: '1',
      c2: '2',
      c3: '8',
      c4: '16',
      answer: '2'),
  QuizBrain(
      question:
          'What is the hemihydrate of calcium sulphate commonly known as?',
      c1: 'Gypsum',
      c2: 'Plaster of Paris',
      c3: 'Chloroform',
      c4: 'Limestone',
      answer: 'Plaster of Paris'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'Which of the following is the purest form of iron?',
      c1: 'Pig iron',
      c2: 'Cast iron',
      c3: 'Wrought iron',
      c4: 'None of the above',
      answer: 'Wrought iron'),
];
List<QuizBrain> mathData = [
  QuizBrain(
      question:
          'The value of cos 0°. cos 1°. cos 2°. cos 3°… cos 89° cos 90° is',
      c1: '1',
      c2: '-1',
      c3: '0',
      c4: '0.5',
      answer: '0'),
  QuizBrain(
      question:
          'The volumes of two spheres are in the ratio 125:64. The ratio of their surface areas is',
      c1: '9:16',
      c2: '16:9',
      c3: '25:16',
      c4: '16:25',
      answer: '25:16'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'A triangle ABC has side a. Its area is',
      c1: 'πa^2',
      c2: '√3a/4',
      c3: '√3a^2/4',
      c4: '3a^2',
      answer: '√3a^2/4'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'Which of the following is not irrational?',
      c1: '(2 – √3)2',
      c2: '(√2 + √3)2',
      c3: '(√2 -√3)(√2 + √3)',
      c4: '2√7/7',
      answer: '(√2 -√3)(√2 + √3)'),
  QuizBrain(
      question:
          'The nth term of an A.P. is given by tn = 3 + 4n. The common difference is',
      c1: '7',
      c2: '3',
      c3: '4',
      c4: '1',
      answer: '4'),
];
List<QuizBrain> gkData = [
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'Who wrote the book- Life of Pi?',
      c1: 'Yann Martel',
      c2: 'George Saunders',
      c3: 'Salman Rushdie',
      c4: 'Amitav Ghosh',
      answer: 'Yann Martel'),
  QuizBrain(
      question:
          'Which of the following planets rotates in a direction opposite to the direction of earth\'s?',
      c1: 'Mars',
      c2: 'Jupiter',
      c3: 'Venus',
      c4: 'Mercury',
      answer: 'Venus'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'Which is the largest island in the world?',
      c1: 'New Guinea',
      c2: 'Borneo',
      c3: 'Madagascar',
      c4: 'Greenland',
      answer: 'Greenland'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'Who wrote the book- A Suitable Boy?',
      c1: 'Salman Rushdie',
      c2: 'Arundhati Roy',
      c3: 'Amitav Ghosh',
      c4: 'Vikram Seth',
      answer: 'Vikram Seth'),
  QuizBrain(
      question: 'A star of which colour can be said to be the coolest?',
      c1: 'Yellow',
      c2: 'Blue',
      c3: 'Red',
      c4: 'Black',
      answer: 'Red'),
];
